Hooman Tabai

hooman.tabai@gmail.com

553 South Glenhurst Dr. Anaheim, Ca 92808

415.438.0089

SUMMARY OF EXPERIENCE

8 years' cross-platform experience in installing and supporting back-end network services.

 4 years' experience understanding today's cloud base solutions, Amazon AWS and Google Aps, follow by learning the programing skills such as Python and JavaScript to gain enough knowledge to create a modern web product from scratch.

EDUCATION

AS Degree in Internet and Web Application Programing, City College of San Francisco.

SKILLS & CERTIFICATIONS

Current Study: JavaScript; React JS

Certificates: Cisco (Routing and Switching); Microsoft Certified (MCTS); CompTIA A+; Net+; Sec+

Programing Languages:Python; Linux Shell Scripting; JavaScript; CSS3; HTML5Cloud Computing:Amazon AWS; Google Aps; Adobe Creative CloudOperating Systems:Windows/Server; Mac OS; Redhat; FOG Server

RECENT EXPERIENCE

IT Specialist. Martin Bauer Group US, Compton, CA (Oct 2018- Current Position)

Maintaining the back-end Network services and providing remote IT support to +150 employees located in multiple sites over the United States of America and Germany.

Help Desk Specialist II. Five Star Networking, Livermore, CA (May 2015- Aug 2017)

Provide IT support as a contractor for Facebook, LinkedIn and PayPal.

IT Technician. Belkorp AG, John Deere, Stockton, CA (July 2014 – May 2015)

Linked eight John Deere dealership across North and Central California over Fiber Optic and provided IT support to 250 users over high speed internet remotely. Install New Cisco IP phone system and centralized the communication system between all eight locations.

Student Help Desk Technician. City College of San Francisco (2013 - 2014)

Provided networking/desktop support and performed mainframe and account maintenance tasks. Earned commendations for teamwork, flexibility and work excellence in providing IT support to students and faculty.

Network Administrator II. NAPEEC Engineering. Tehran, Ir (2006 – 2012)

Managed all IT and Network services for this multi-national engineering firm. Evaluated, designed and installed gigabyte backbone LAN/WAN Network for over 30 end-users. Developed and managed company's annual IT budget. Provided installation support and for workstations.

Interests & Hobbies

Auto Mechanic | Photography | Hiking | Travel | DJ